<!DOCTYPE document PUBLIC
  "-//Apache Software Foundation//DTD XDOC 1.0//EN"
  "http://maven.apache.org/dtd/xdoc_1_0.dtd">


<document>
  <properties>
    <title>Functions: FnToDateTime</title>    
  </properties>
  <body>
  
    <section name="Functions: FnToDateTime">

      

      <subsection name="1. Overview">

        <p>
            <b><a href="http://www.op4j.org/apidocs/op4j-jodatime/org/op4j/jodatime/functions/FnToDateTime.html">FnToDateTime</a></b> is a <em>function hub class</em>
            containing a lot of static methods to convert from various input objects to DateTime. Those static methods return functions whose 
            output is DateTime and whose input can be Calendar, Date, Integer list and Long among others.             
        </p>
        
      </subsection>

      <subsection name="2. Functions">


<table border="0">
<thead><tr><th>Function name</th><th>Type</th><th width="240px">Params</th><th>Description</th></tr></thead>
<tbody>
<tr class="b"><td><b>fromCalendar</b></td><td>CalendarToDateTime&lt;T&gt;</td><td>DateTimeZone dateTimeZone</td><td>It converts a  Calendar into a  DateTime in the given  DateTimeZone</td></tr>
<tr class="a"><td><b>fromCalendar</b></td><td>CalendarToDateTime&lt;T&gt;</td><td>Chronology chronology</td><td>It converts a  Calendar into a  DateTime with the given  Chronology</td></tr>
<tr bgcolor="#A4A4A4" class=""><td bgcolor="#A4A4A4" colspan="4"></td></tr>
<tr class="b"><td><b>fromDate</b></td><td>DateToDateTime&lt;T&gt;</td><td>DateTimeZone dateTimeZone</td><td>The given  Date is converted into a  DateTime configured with the given  DateTimeZone</td></tr>
<tr class="a"><td><b>fromDate</b></td><td>DateToDateTime&lt;T&gt;</td><td>Chronology chronology</td><td>The given  Date is converted into a  DateTime with the given  Chronology</td></tr>
<tr bgcolor="#A4A4A4" class=""><td bgcolor="#A4A4A4" colspan="4"></td></tr>
<tr class="b"><td><b>fromIntegerFieldArray</b></td><td>IntegerFieldArrayToDateTime</td><td>Chronology chronology</td><td>A  DateTime is created from the given  Integer array. Year, month, day can be used. If not all of them set, the last ones will be set to 1 The result will be created with the given  Chronology</td></tr>
<tr bgcolor="#A4A4A4" class=""><td bgcolor="#A4A4A4" colspan="4"></td></tr>
<tr class="a"><td><b>fromIntegerFieldCollection</b></td><td>IntegerFieldCollectionToDateTime</td><td>Chronology chronology</td><td>A  DateTime is created from the given  Integer  Collection. Year, month, day can be used. If not all of them set, the last ones will be set to 1 The result will be created with the given  Chronology</td></tr>
<tr bgcolor="#A4A4A4" class=""><td bgcolor="#A4A4A4" colspan="4"></td></tr>
<tr class="b"><td><b>fromLong</b></td><td>LongToDateTime</td><td>DateTimeZone dateTimeZone</td><td>The given  Long representing the time in milliseconds is converted into a  DateTime in the given  DateTimeZone</td></tr>
<tr class="a"><td><b>fromLong</b></td><td>LongToDateTime</td><td>Chronology chronology</td><td>The given  Long representing the time in milliseconds is converted into a  DateTime with the given  Chronology</td></tr>
<tr bgcolor="#A4A4A4" class=""><td bgcolor="#A4A4A4" colspan="4"></td></tr>
<tr class="b"><td><b>fromString</b></td><td>StringToDateTime</td><td>String pattern</td><td>It converts the given  String into a  DateTime using the  given pattern parameter. If the pattern includes either, the name of  the month or day of week, a conversion accepting a  Locale must  be used instead</td></tr>
<tr class="a"><td><b>fromString</b></td><td>StringToDateTime</td><td>String pattern<br />DateTimeZone dateTimeZone</td><td>It converts the given  String into a  DateTime using the given pattern parameter and with the given  DateTimeZone. If the pattern includes either, the name of the month or day of week, a conversion accepting a  Locale must be used instead</td></tr>
<tr class="b"><td><b>fromString</b></td><td>StringToDateTime</td><td>String pattern<br />Chronology chronology</td><td>It converts the given  String into a  DateTime using the given pattern parameter and with the given  Chronology. If the pattern includes either, the name of the month or day of week, a conversion accepting a  Locale must be used instead</td></tr>
<tr class="a"><td><b>fromString</b></td><td>StringToDateTime</td><td>String pattern<br />Locale locale</td><td>It converts the given  String into a  DateTime using the given pattern and  Locale parameters</td></tr>
<tr class="b"><td><b>fromString</b></td><td>StringToDateTime</td><td>String pattern<br />String locale</td><td>It converts the given  String into a  DateTime using the given pattern and  Locale parameters</td></tr>
<tr class="a"><td><b>fromString</b></td><td>StringToDateTime</td><td>String pattern<br />Locale locale<br />DateTimeZone dateTimeZone</td><td>It converts the given String into a  DateTime using the given pattern and  Locale parameters. The  DateTime is configured with the given  DateTimeZone</td></tr>
<tr class="b"><td><b>fromString</b></td><td>StringToDateTime</td><td>String pattern<br />String locale<br />DateTimeZone dateTimeZone</td><td>It converts the given  String into a  DateTime using the given pattern and  Locale parameters. The  DateTime is configured with the given  DateTimeZone</td></tr>
<tr class="a"><td><b>fromString</b></td><td>StringToDateTime</td><td>String pattern<br />Locale locale<br />Chronology chronology</td><td>It converts the given  String into a  DateTime using the given pattern and  Locale parameters. The  DateTime will be created with the given  Chronology</td></tr>
<tr class="b"><td><b>fromString</b></td><td>StringToDateTime</td><td>String pattern<br />String locale<br />Chronology chronology</td><td>It converts the given String into a  DateTime using the given pattern and  Locale parameters. The  DateTime will be created with the given  Chronology</td></tr>
<tr bgcolor="#A4A4A4" class=""><td bgcolor="#A4A4A4" colspan="4"></td></tr>
<tr class="a"><td><b>fromStringFieldArray</b></td><td>StringFieldArrayToDateTime</td><td>Chronology chronology</td><td>A  DateTime is created from the given  String array. Year, month, day can be used. If not all of them set, the last ones will be set to 1 The result will be created with the given  Chronology</td></tr>
<tr bgcolor="#A4A4A4" class=""><td bgcolor="#A4A4A4" colspan="4"></td></tr>
<tr class="b"><td><b>fromStringFieldCollection</b></td><td>StringFieldCollectionToDateTime</td><td>Chronology chronology</td><td>A  DateTime is created from the given  String  Collection. Year, month, day can be used. If not all of them set, the last ones will be set to 1 The result will be created with the given  Chronology</td></tr>
<tr bgcolor="#A4A4A4" class=""><td bgcolor="#A4A4A4" colspan="4"></td></tr>
<tr class="a"><td><b>fromTimestamp</b></td><td>TimestampToDateTime</td><td>DateTimeZone dateTimeZone</td><td>The given  Timestamp is converted into a  DateTime in the given  DateTimeZone</td></tr>
<tr class="b"><td><b>fromTimestamp</b></td><td>TimestampToDateTime</td><td>Chronology chronology</td><td>The given  Timestamp is converted into a  DateTime with the given  Chronology</td></tr>
</tbody></table>

      </subsection>
      
    </section>
  </body>
</document>
